WAMC Northeast Public Radio; Records apap138
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- The Environment Show, 1990-2000
  - The Environment Show #411, 1997 November 15
  - The Environment Show #412, 1997 November 22
  - The Environment Show #413, 1997 November 24
  - The Environment Show #414, 1997 December 6
  - The Environment Show #415, 1997 December 13
  - The Environment Show #416, 1997 December 17
  - The Environment Show #417, 1997 December 27
  - The Environment Show #418, 1998 January 3
  - The Environment Show #419, 1998 January 10
  - The Environment Show #420, 1998 January 17
  - The Environment Show #421, 1998 January 24
  - The Environment Show #422, 1998 January 31
  - The Environment Show #423, 1998 February 7
  - The Environment Show #424, 1998 February 14
  - The Environment Show #425, 1998 February 21
  - The Environment Show #426, 1998 February 28
  - The Environment Show #427, 1998 March 7
  - The Environment Show #428, 1998 March 11
  - The Environment Show #429, 1998 March 18
  - The Environment Show #430, 1998 March 25
  - The Environment Show #431, 1998 March 31
  - The Environment Show #432, 1998 April 11
  - The Environment Show #433, 1998 April 18
  - The Environment Show #434, 1998 April 21
  - The Environment Show #435, 1998 April 28
  - The Environment Show #436, 1998 May 5
  - The Environment Show #437, 1998 May 12
  - The Environment Show #438, 1998 May 19
  - The Environment Show #439, 1998 May 26
  - The Environment Show #440, 1998 June 2
  - The Environment Show #441, 1998 June 9
  - The Environment Show #442, 1998 June 17
  - The Environment Show #469, 1998 December 22
  - The Environment Show #470, 1998 December 28
  - The Environment Show #471, 1999 January 6
  - The Environment Show #472, 1999 January 13
  - The Environment Show #473, 1999 January 23
  - The Environment Show #474, 1999 January 30
  - The Environment Show #475, 1999 February 6
  - The Environment Show #476, 1999 February 13
  - The Environment Show #477, 1999 February 20
  - The Environment Show #478, 1999 February 27
  - The Environment Show #479, 1999 March 6
  - The Environment Show #480, 1999 March 13
  - The Environment Show #481, 1999 March 20
  - The Environment Show #482, 1999 March 27
  - The Environment Show #483, 1999 April 3
  - The Environment Show #484, 1999 April 10
  - The Environment Show #485, 1999 April 17
  - The Environment Show #486, 1999 April 24
  - The Environment Show #487, 1999 May 1
  - The Environment Show #488, 1999 May 8
  - The Environment Show #490, 1999 May 15
  - The Environment Show #491, 1999 May 29
  - The Environment Show #492, 1999 June 5
  - The Environment Show #493, 1999 June 12
  - The Environment Show #494, 1999 June 19
  - The Environment Show #495, 1999 June 26
  - The Environment Show #496, 1999 July 3
  - The Environment Show #497, 1999 July 10
  - The Environment Show #498, 1999 July 17
  - The Environment Show #499, 1999 July 24
  - The Environment Show #500, 1999 July 31
  - The Environment Show #501, 1999 August 7
  - The Environment Show #502, 1999 August 14
  - The Environment Show #503, 1999 August 21
  - The Environment Show #504, 1999 August 28
  - The Environment Show #505, 1999 September 4
  - The Environment Show #506, 1999 September 11
  - The Environment Show #507, 1999 September 18
  - The Environment Show #508, 1999 September 21
  - The Environment Show #509, 1999 September 28
  - The Environment Show #510, 1999 October 5
  - The Environment Show #511, 1999 October 12
  - The Environment Show #512, 1999 October 19
  - The Environment Show #513, 1999 October 26
  - The Environment Show #514, 1999 November 6
  - The Environment Show #515, 1999 November 13
  - The Environment Show #516, 1999 November 16
  - The Environment Show #517, 1999 November 22
  - The Environment Show #518, 1999 November 30
  - The Environment Show #519, 1999 December 7
  - The Environment Show #523, 2000 January 4
  - The Environment Show #524, 2000 January 11
  - The Environment Show #525, 2000 January 18
- The Health Show, 2012-2013
  Contains recorded broadcasts of The Health Show, a WAMC-produced weekly radio show hosted by Bob Barrett and Dr. Nina Sax that aims to better inform patients and health care providers. The program covers all aspects of modern health: prevention, treatment, research, administration and more.
  - The Health Show Show 1290, 2012 December 19
  - The Health Show Show 1291, 2012 December 26
  - The Health Show Show 1292, 2013 January 2
  - The Health Show Show 1293, 2013 January 9
  - The Health Show Show 1294, 2013 January 16
  - The Health Show Show 1295, 2013 January 23
  - The Health Show Show 1296, 2013 January 30
  - The Health Show Show 1297, 2013 February 6
  - The Health Show Show 1298, 2013 February 13
  - The Health Show Show 1299, 2013 February 20
  - The Health Show Show 1300, 2013 February 27
  - The Health Show Show 1301, 2013 March 6
  - The Health Show Show 1302, 2013 March 13
  - The Health Show Show 1303, 2013 March 20
  - The Health Show Show 1304, 2013 March 27
  - The Health Show Show 1305, 2013 April 3
  - The Health Show Show 1306, 2013 April 10
  - The Health Show Show 1307, 2013 April 17
  - The Health Show Show 1308, 2013 April 24
  - The Health Show Show 1309, 2013 May 1
  - The Health Show Show 1310, 2013 May 8
  - The Health Show Show 1311, 2013 May 15
  - The Health Show Show 1312, 2013 May 22
  - The Health Show Show 1313, 2013 May 29
  - The Health Show Show 1314, 2013 June 5
  - The Health Show Show 1315, 2013 June 12
  - The Health Show Show 1316, 2013 June 19
  - The Health Show Show 1317, 2013 June 26
- The Best of Our Knowledge, 2012-2013
  Contains recorded broadcasts of The Best Of Our Knowledge, a WAMC-produced weekly radio show hosted by Bob Barrett that highlights breakthroughs across academic disciplines. Each week this program examines some of the issues unique to college campuses, looks at the latest research, and invites commentary from experts and administrators from all levels of education.
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1162, 2012 December 25
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1163, 2013 January 1
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1164, 2013 January 8
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1165, 2013 January 15
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1166, 2013 January 22
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1167, 2013 January 29
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1168, 2013 February 5
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1169, 2013 February 12
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1170, 2013 February 19
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1171, 2013 February 26
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1172, 2013 March 5
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1173, 2013 March 12
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1174, 2013 March 19
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1175, 2013 March 26
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1176, 2013 April 2
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1177, 2013 April 9
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1178, 2013 April 16
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1179, 2013 April 23
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1180, 2013 April 30
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1181, 2013 May 7
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1182, 2013 May 14
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1183, 2013 May 21
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1184, 2013 May 28
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1186, 2013 June 11
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1187, 2013 June 18
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1188, 2013 June 25
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1189, 2013 July 2
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1190, 2013 July 9
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1191, 2013 July 16
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1192, 2013 July 23
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1193, 2013 July 30
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1194, 2013 August 6
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1195, 2013 August 13
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1196, 2013 August 20
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1197, 2013 August 27
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1198, 2013 September 3
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1199, 2013 September 10
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1200, 2013 September 17
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1201, 2013 September 24
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1202, 2013 October 1
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1203, 2013 October 8
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1204, 2013 October 15
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1205, 2013 October 22
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1206, 2013 October 29
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1207, 2013 November 5
  - The Best of Our Knowledge Show 1208, 2013 November 12
- 51%, 2012-2013
  Contains recorded broadcasts of 51%, a WAMC-produced weekly radio show hosted by Allison Dunne that discusses women's perpectives on the environment, health, children, politics, the arts, and more.
  - 51% Show 1224, 2012 December 28
  - 51% Show 1225, 2013 January 4
  - 51% Show 1226, 2013 January 11
  - 51% Show 1229, 2013 February 1
  - 51% Show 1230, 2013 February 8
  - 51% Show 1231, 2013 February 15
  - 51% Show 1232, 2013 February 22
  - 51% Show 1233, 2013 March 1
  - 51% Show 1234, 2013 March 8
  - 51% Show 1235, 2013 March 15
  - 51% Show 1236, 2013 March 22
  - 51% Show 1237, 2013 March 29
  - 51% Show 1238, 2013 April 5
  - 51% Show 1239, 2013 April 12
  - 51% Show 1240, 2013 April 19
  - 51% Show 1241, 2013 April 26
  - 51% Show 1242, 2013 May 3
  - 51% Show 1243, 2013 May 10
  - 51% Show 1244, 2013 May 17
  - 51% Show 1245, 2013 May 24
  - 51% Show 1246, 2013 May 31
  - 51% Show 1248, 2013 June 13
  - 51% Show 1249, 2013 June 20
  - 51% Show 1250, 2013 June 27
  - 51% Show 1251, 2013 July 4
  - 51% Show 1252, 2013 July 11
  - 51% Show 1253, 2013 July 18
  - 51% Show 1254, 2013 July 25
  - 51% Show 1255, 2013 August 1
  - 51% Show 1256, 2013 August 8
  - 51% Show 1257, 2013 August 15
  - 51% Show 1258, 2013 August 22
  - 51% Show 1259, 2013 August 29
  - 51% Show 1260, 2013 September 5
  - 51% Show 1261, 2013 September 12
  - 51% Show 1262, 2013 September 19
  - 51% Show 1263, 2013 September 26
  - 51% Show 1264, 2013 October 3
  - 51% Show 1265, 2013 October 10
- The Capitol Connection, 2012-2014
  Contains recorded broadcasts of The Capitol Connection, a WAMC-produced weekly radio show that covers New York State politics. Host Alan Chartock commonly interviews members of the New York State Senate and Assembly or other politicians and activists.
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1251, 2012 December 21
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1252, 2012 December 28
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1315, 2013 April 12
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1316, 2013 April 19
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1317, 2013 April 26
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1314, 2013 April 5
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1333, 2013 August 16
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1331, 2013 August 2
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1334, 2013 August 23
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1332, 2013 August 9
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1350, 2013 December 13
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1351, 2013 December 20
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1352, 2013 December 27
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1349, 2013 December 6
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1305, 2013 February 1
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1307, 2013 February 15
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1308, 2013 February 22
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1306, 2013 February 8
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1302, 2013 January 11
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1303, 2013 January 18
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1304, 2013 January 25
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1301, 2013 January 4
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1328, 2013 July 12
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1329, 2013 July 19
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1330, 2013 July 26
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1327, 2013 July 5
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1324, 2013 June 14
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1325, 2013 June 21
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1326, 2013 June 28
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1323, 2013 June 6
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1309, 2013 March 1
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1311, 2013 March 15
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1312, 2013 March 22
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1313, 2013 March 29
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1310, 2013 March 8
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1319, 2013 May 10
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1320, 2013 May 17
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1321, 2013 May 24
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1318, 2013 May 3
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1344, 2013 November 1
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1346, 2013 November 15
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1347, 2013 November 22
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1348, 2013 November 29
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1345, 2013 November 8
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1341, 2013 October 11
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1342, 2013 October 18
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1343, 2013 October 25
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1340, 2013 October 4
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1337, 2013 September 13
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1338, 2013 September 20
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1339, 2013 September 27
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1336, 2013 September 6
  - The Capitol Connection Show 1401, 2014 January 3
- The Media Project, 2012-2014
  Contains recorded broadcasts of The Media Project, a WAMC-produced weekly radio show that provides an inside look at media coverage of current events. Panelists include Times Union Editor Rex Smith, WAMC CEO and UAlban Alan S. Chartock, and Daily Freeman Publisher Ira Fusfeld.
  - The Media Project 1125, 2012 December 23
  - The Media Project 1126, 2012 December 30
  - The Media Project 1127, 2013 January 6
  - The Media Project 1128, 2013 January 13
  - The Media Project 1129, 2013 January 20
  - The Media Project 1130, 2013 January 27
  - The Media Project 1131, 2013 February 3
  - The Media Project 1132, 2013 February 10
  - The Media Project 1133, 2013 February 17
  - The Media Project 1134, 2013 February 24
  - The Media Project 1135, 2013 March 3
  - The Media Project 1136, 2013 March 10
  - The Media Project 1137, 2013 March 17
  - The Media Project 1138, 2013 March 24
  - The Media Project 1139, 2013 March 31
  - The Media Project 1140, 2013 April 7
  - The Media Project 1141, 2013 April 14
  - The Media Project 1142, 2013 April 21
  - The Media Project 1143, 2013 April 28
  - The Media Project 1144, 2013 May 5
  - The Media Project 1145, 2013 May 12
  - The Media Project 1146, 2013 May 19
  - The Media Project 1147, 2013 May 26
  - The Media Project 1149, 2013 June 9
  - The Media Project 1150, 2013 June 16
  - The Media Project 1151, 2013 June 23
  - The Media Project 1152, 2013 June 30
  - The Media Project 1153, 2013 July 7
  - The Media Project 1154, 2013 July 14
  - The Media Project 1155, 2013 July 21
  - The Media Project 1156, 2013 July 28
  - The Media Project 1157, 2013 August 4
  - The Media Project 1158, 2013 August 11
  - The Media Project 1159, 2013 August 18
  - The Media Project 1160, 2013 August 25
  - The Media Project 1161, 2013 September 1
  - The Media Project 1162, 2013 September 8
  - The Media Project 1163, 2013 September 15
  - The Media Project 1164, 2013 September 22
  - The Media Project 1165, 2013 September 29
  - The Media Project 1166, 2013 October 6
  - The Media Project 1167, 2013 October 13
  - The Media Project 1168, 2013 October 20
  - The Media Project 1169, 2013 October 27
  - The Media Project 1170, 2013 November 3
  - The Media Project 1171, 2013 November 10
  - The Media Project 1172, 2013 November 17
  - The Media Project 1173, 2013 November 24
  - The Media Project 1174, 2013 December 1
  - The Media Project 1175, 2013 December 8
  - The Media Project 1176, 2013 December 15
  - The Media Project 1177, 2013 December 22
  - The Media Project 1178, 2013 December 29
  - The Media Project 1179, 2014 January 5
- The Book Show, 2012-2014
  Contains recorded broadcasts of The Book Show, a WAMC-produced weekly radio show hosted by Joe Donahue thet interviews authors about their books, their lives and their craft. Notable authors interviewed include: Kurt Vonnegut, John Irving, John Updike, Alice Walker, Toni Morrison, Arthur Miller, Stephen King, Amy Tan, Anne Rice, Philip Roth, E.L Doctorow, Richard Russo, David Sedaris and Maya Angelou.
  - The Book Show Show 1275, 2012 December 23
  - The Book Show Show 1276, 2012 December 30
  - The Book Show Show 1277, 2013 January 6
  - The Book Show Show 1278, 2013 January 13
  - The Book Show Show 1279, 2013 January 20
  - The Book Show Show 1280, 2013 January 27
  - The Book Show Show 1281, 2013 February 3
  - The Book Show Show 1282, 2013 February 10
  - The Book Show Show 1283, 2013 February 17
  - The Book Show Show 1284, 2013 February 24
  - The Book Show Show 1285, 2013 March 3
  - The Book Show Show 1286, 2013 March 10
  - The Book Show Show 1287, 2013 March 17
  - The Book Show Show 1288, 2013 March 24
  - The Book Show Show 1289, 2013 March 31
  - The Book Show Show 1290, 2013 April 7
  - The Book Show Show 1291, 2013 April 14
  - The Book Show Show 1292, 2013 April 21
  - The Book Show Show 1293, 2013 April 28
  - The Book Show Show 1294, 2013 May 5
  - The Book Show Show 1295, 2013 May 12
  - The Book Show Show 1296, 2013 May 19
  - The Book Show Show 1297, 2013 May 26
  - The Book Show Show 1299, 2013 June 9
  - The Book Show Show 1300, 2013 June 16
  - The Book Show Show 1301, 2013 June 23
  - The Book Show Show 1302, 2013 June 30
  - The Book Show Show 1303, 2013 July 7
  - The Book Show Show 1304, 2013 July 14
  - The Book Show Show 1305, 2013 July 21
  - The Book Show Show 1306, 2013 July 28
  - The Book Show Show 1307, 2013 August 4
  - The Book Show Show 1308, 2013 August 11
  - The Book Show Show 1309, 2013 August 18
  - The Book Show Show 1310, 2013 August 25
  - The Book Show Show 1311, 2013 September 1
  - The Book Show Show 1312, 2013 September 8
  - The Book Show Show 1313, 2013 September 15
  - The Book Show Show 1314, 2013 September 22
  - The Book Show Show 1315, 2013 September 29
  - The Book Show Show 1316, 2013 October 6
  - The Book Show Show 1317, 2013 October 13
  - The Book Show Show 1318, 2013 October 20
  - The Book Show Show 1319, 2013 October 27
  - The Book Show Show 1320, 2013 November 3
  - The Book Show Show 1321, 2013 November 10
  - The Book Show Show 1322, 2013 November 17
  - The Book Show Show 1323, 2013 November 24
  - The Book Show Show 1324, 2013 December 1
  - The Book Show Show 1325, 2013 December 8
  - The Book Show Show 1326, 2013 December 15
  - The Book Show Show 1327, 2013 December 22
  - The Book Show Show 1328, 2013 December 29
  - The Book Show Show 1329, 2014 January 4